dare.co.in 2009-04-05

# Privacy Policy | Privacy Policy | Home | DARE - Because Entrepreneurs Do |

[ Home ](http://dare.co.in/table/home/) \-  [ Privacy Policy ](http://dare.co.in/table/home/privacy-policy/)  
Written by DARE      
Tuesday, 01 July 2008 13:49   
  
**Our commitment to your privacy **  
Your privacy is important to us. This document outlines  what information we collect about you and how we use it.

**What information do we collect?**  
DARE is a magazine dedicated to the entrepreneur ecosystem in India. You can order subscriptions of the print magazine, send feedback, participate in surveys, make requests, register to receive updates, make comments or request for assistance in your entrepreneurial ventures.  
The personal information we collect include - Name, Address, Email address and Phone number for print subscriptions and Name and email address for comments at this site. For our surveys, we may collect additional demographic and business related information. When you use your credit card to subscribe to DARE at this website, we do not collect or store your credit card information. You will be transferred to our merchant banker’s secure site for the transaction.

**How do we use the information?**  
We do not share your personal, identifiable information or the information that you provide, with outside parties (entrepreneurs, investors, advertisers, etc.) except when you permit us to.  
We use your email addresses to answer your queries and to send regular updates about the site, the publication or related events. Occasionally, we do send you offers from our partners, but your email id or other personal information is never shared with outside parties. Please note that if you choose to answer such offers, you contact information, etc. becomes available to them.  
Any information you share in our surveys is used only in aggregate and no information that can identify you will be shared or disclosed without your permission.  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example,  depending on the location of our visitors, and the pages  that they visit, we will try and redesign the site so as to make it more easy for you to navigate. Or, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of entrepreneurs have asked us a question on funding; but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

**Data security  
** To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**For children  
** The site contains no information or content that could be useful to children below 13 years of age. Nor does it carry any information detrimental to children. We do not encourage children to participate in our discussions. However, given that we provide facilities for our readers to add their comments to our articles and blogs, it is possible that some comments not suitable for a young audience may occasionally creep in. While all attempts will be made to moderate them out, reader caution is advised.

**Contact us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at dare@cybermedia.co.in.

Our postal address is  
CyberMedia India ltd.  
Cyber House  
B 35, Sector 32  
Gurgaon 122001  
NCR – Delhi  
India
